{
    "id": "7f3626a64e6c4c759f243cdf2a902961",
    "title": "Modal Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………… you touch your toes without bending your knees?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Can",
                "May",
                "Shall"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… like to offer a piece of advice.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "could",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………….. you mind moving a bit?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Can",
                "Would",
                "May"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. I leave now?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Can",
                "May",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………….. be sick your eyes are red and watery.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "can",
                "must"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………….. not drink and drive.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "ought",
                "need"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… you like to have a glass of milk?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Can",
                "Would",
                "Should"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………….. have been in a lot of pain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "must",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………. build a rain water harvesting system.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "must",
                "ought to",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "We ...................... consume a lot of sugar, but now we have given up that habit.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "used",
                "used to",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Who ………………… it be?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "can",
                "may"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There ………………… be something wrong with him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "ought",
                "must"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}